gap.com 2017-05-21

# | Gap

## Privacy Policy

_Last Revised March 13, 2017_

This policy describes the personal information Gap Inc. and our brands, which include but are not limited to Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory, Banana Republic Factory, and Athleta (collectively, "Gap Inc.") collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Please note that this policy does not cover the data collection and use practices of Weddington Way, as described further, below. For full details on how Weddington Way may collect, use and share your personal information, please see Weddington Way’s [Privacy Policy](https://www.weddingtonway.com/privacy_policy). 

This policy covers our US stores and online experiences including our websites and mobile apps and other webpages and services which we operate and in which we post a direct link to this policy. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears above. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

  * What kind of information does Gap Inc. collect?
  * How does Gap Inc. use my information?
  * How does Gap Inc. share my information?
  * What other information does Gap Inc. collect?
  * What if I connect to Gap Inc.’s in-store Wi-Fi services?
  * What if I use different devices to visit Gap Inc. websites or mobile applications?
  * Why did I receive a marketing email after I made a purchase in a Gap Inc. store?
  * How do I access or change my information?
  * How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?
  * How do I stop receiving Athleta catalogs?
  * What if I interact or make a purchase with Weddington Way?
  * How does Gap Inc. protect kids' privacy?
  * How is my information used for behavioral or targeted advertising and what choices do I have?
  * What if I apply for a Gap Inc. branded credit card on your site?
  * What if I participate in local store programs?
  * How do I know my personal information is secure?
  * What is "phishing"?
  * I received a suspicious email from a Gap Inc. brand regarding an order I did not place. What should I do?
  * I responded to an online job posting for a Gap Inc. job that requires me to upload personal financial information. Is this part of your hiring process?
  * What about links to other websites?
  * How do I contact you?
  * Your California Privacy Rights

### What kind of information does Gap Inc. collect?

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number, gender, birthday, personal interests, etc., when you visit one of our websites or stores, install or use our mobile apps, place an order online or by phone, make an in-store purchase, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online, through a mobile app, by phone and in our stores.

We may combine personal information with information about your online and in-store transactions and other interactions with us, including your purchases. We may also combine your personal information with information we receive from other sources, such as joint marketing partners, public databases, publicly available pages on social media platforms and other third parties. In addition, if you choose to engage in social sharing, such as by connecting your social media account to your customer account or by logging into your customer account from your social media account, the social media site may share information with us about your use of their services, including profile information, information about your contacts and content you have viewed or liked. Please refer to the social media site’s privacy settings to control how your information is shared.

If you submit any personal information relating to other people to us or to our service providers, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

back to top

### How does Gap Inc. use my information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment
  * To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, including marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you
  * To make your shopping experience easier, more enjoyable and more efficient
  * To address problems with and improve our products, brands, services and technologies, as well as to develop new products and services
  * To allow you to use our in-store and online technologies
  * To provide consistent, personalized services across all channels and all of our brands, including to personalize our advertising, marketing communications, shopping experiences and promotional offers
  * To organize local community events, promotions and in-store experiences
  * To facilitate social sharing 
  * To allow you to apply for an offer of credit from a payment card provider
  * To allow you to enroll and participate in a loyalty or customer relationship program 
  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions
  * To help us learn more about your shopping preferences
  * To prevent, detect, mitigate and investigate fraud, security breaches and activities that are or potentially may be prohibited or illegal
  * To enforce our [Terms of Use](http://www.gap.com/customerService/info.do?cid=6754) or other policies
  * As we believe to be required or appropriate to protect the rights, property, safety and security of Gap Inc. and our employees, customers and others
  * As we believe to be required or appropriate under applicable law, to respond to requests from government authorities and to comply with legal process

You always have the choice not to receive marketing information or calls. For instructions on opting out, please see the section entitled, "How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?", below.

back to top

### How does Gap Inc. share my information?

We may share your personal information in the following ways:

  * **Brands.** When you provide personal information to one of our Gap Inc. brands (Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory, Banana Republic Factory, Athleta, or Intermix), we may share that information with our other Gap Inc. brands. 
  * **Direct Mail.** If you purchase Athleta brand products through our website or by placing a catalog order by phone or mail, we may share your name, postal address, and shopping history with like-minded organizations for their direct mail marketing purposes. We do not share email addresses for such purposes. We also do not share personal information about customers who only browse, email comments, request a catalog, or request email updates, or who purchase only Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory, Banana Republic Factory, or Intermix merchandise. If you would prefer that we not share information about you with other companies, please let us know by contacting Athleta customer service as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.
  * **By You.** You may disclose personal information when you post content to our websites, in-store technologies or other public forums, such as our brands’ social media pages, blogs, and online product reviews. Any information that you disclose through these services will become public. 
  * **Social Sharing.** Your personal information may be disclosed in connection with your social sharing activity, such as if you log into your customer account from your social media account. By connecting your customer account and your social media account, you authorize us to share information with your social media account provider, and you understand that the use of the information we share will be governed by the social media site’s privacy policy. 
  * **Service Providers.** We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information. 

**Third Parties.** We may share your information when we team up with another company to offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers. 

  * **Legal Requirements.** We may share information about you if necessary or appropriate, in our good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the operations, privacy, safety, property or rights of Gap Inc. or others.
  * **Scrip or Loyalty Programs.** If you choose to participate in any third-party scrip, loyalty, or similar program in which a Gap Inc. brand is a participating vendor, and you authorize Gap Inc. or our credit card processor to provide information about your purchases to the company administering the program, we will share your personal information with that program. Scrip programs allow you to instruct us to divert a percentage of the amount you spend on Gap Inc. purchases to participating schools and other non-profit organizations. Loyalty programs allow you to earn "points" on purchases at Gap Inc. brands, which you may then use toward certain rewards offered by the loyalty programs in which you participate. The information you authorize us to disclose to the third-party scrip or loyalty program may include your credit card number and the date and amount of your purchase, and may also include your name and other information you have asked us to provide. Please note that once we disclose this information, the scrip or loyalty company may use and share it with others in accordance with its own privacy policy. You should review these policies carefully, as we have no control over them.
  * **Business Transfer.** In the unlikely event of a sale or merger of Gap Inc. or any of our businesses, our customers' personal information and other information we have collected as described in this policy may be among the transferred business assets.

back to top

### What other information does Gap Inc. collect?

We may collect information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as browser and device information; information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies, demographic information and other information provided by you; and aggregated information.

We may use and disclose such information for any lawful purpose. If required, we will treat such information as personal information in accordance with this policy. We will also treat such information as personal information to the extent it is combined with personal information. For example, when you use our technologies, we may keep a record of your product interests, the purchases you make and other content you generate (such as adding items to your shopping cart). 

We may collect information in a variety of ways, including:

  * **Your browser or device:** Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language, Internet browser type and version, and browser click-through and usage data. 
  * **Mobile applications:** When you download and use one of our mobile applications, we may track and collect usage data, such as the date and time the app on your device accesses our servers and what information and files have been accessed, viewed and/or downloaded to the app based on your device number or other identifier. 
  * **Cookies:** Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using. Our websites, online advertisements, and emails use cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies to automatically collect information about your interactions, such as browser type, pages viewed, links clicked, and other actions you take in connection with our websites, online ads, and email. We use the information for a variety of purposes, including to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, to personalize your experience, to understand how our websites are used, to measure the success of our marketing campaigns, and for security purposes. If your browser is set to decline cookies, you may not be able to access your customer account or make a purchase on our websites. To learn how we use cookies for advertising, please see the section, “How is my information used for behavioral or targeted advertising and what choices do I have?” below.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site. If you do not accept cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of our sites. For example, you may not be able to access your account information or make a purchase on our websites.

  * **Using pixel tags and other similar technologies:** We may use pixel tags to, among other things, track the actions of users of our sites and services (including email recipients), measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of our sites and services and response rates. 
  * **Analytics:** We use third-party service providers, including Google and Adobe, which use cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of our websites and mobile applications and in-store technologies. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps and online resources. You can learn about Google’s practices at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>, and opt out by using the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on, available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. You can learn about Adobe’s practices and opt out at <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>.
  * **Adobe Flash:** We may use Adobe Flash technology, including Flash Local Shared Objects (“Flash LSOs”), and other similar technologies to collect and store information about your use of our websites and mobile applications. You can adjust your Flash player settings to block Flash LSO storage on your computer using the tools contained in the [Website Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). You can also control Flash LSOs by going to the [Global Storage Settings Panel](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html) and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash LSOs (referred to as “information” on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without you being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash LSOs that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time). Please note that setting the Flash Player to limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may interfere with the functionality of some Flash applications, including those used in connection with our websites and mobile apps.
  * **IP Address:** Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet service provider. An IP address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever you access our websites, along with the time of the visit and the pages that were visited. Your IP address may also indicate your approximate physical location. Collecting IP addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other technologies. We use IP addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels and diagnosing server problems. 
  * **Physical Location:** We may collect the physical location of your device by, for example, using satellite, cell phone tower or Wi-Fi signals. We may use your device’s physical location to provide you with personalized location-based services and content. You may be permitted to allow or deny such uses, but if you do deny them, we may not be able to provide you with a personalized user experience. 
  * **In-Store Technologies:** We may provide in-store technologies to help personalize and improve your shopping experience. These technologies may require the collection of certain information about your mobile device, such as your MAC address or other device identification information and may also permit you to submit personal details for increased levels of personalization, such as your interests, shopping preferences, and sizing information. 
  * **Aggregated information:** We may collect and use aggregated personal information, which does not personally identify you. For example, we may calculate the percentage of our site users who have a particular telephone area code.

back to top

### What if I connect to Gap Inc.’s in-store Wi-Fi services?

If you choose to connect to our in-store Wi-Fi services, Gap Inc. will receive information about you and your device, including your device’s MAC address, IP address, received signal strength indicator (RSSI) and technical details about your device such as its operating system and device type (including make and model) and technical capabilities. If you have given your device a name, we may receive it. We will also receive information about how you use our Wi-Fi network while you are connected, including the store location, the areas of the store you visit, the names and/or Internet addresses of the websites you visit and the applications you use, and how long you interact with such sites or applications. We collect this information each time you connect to the Wi-Fi services and may associate it with other information we have collected from and about you. 

If your mobile device is configured to search for available Wi-Fi networks, we may receive information about your device even if you choose not to connect to our Wi-Fi services. 

As a convenience, we may provide you with an option to stay connected to the Gap Inc. Wi-Fi networks. If you choose this option, you will be automatically logged into the Wi-Fi network of any Gap Inc. store offering Wi-Fi services, and we may collect the information described above even if you do not actively use your Internet browser or your mobile applications during your time in our store. You can choose to disconnect from the Gap Wi-Fi network at any time through your device’s Wi-Fi settings. However, please note that disconnecting from one store’s Wi-Fi network will only disconnect you from that network during your current visit. You can opt out of the auto-reconnect feature at any time by visiting [http://www.smart-places.org](http://www.smart-places.org/).

For full details about our in-store Wi-Fi practices, please see our [Wi-Fi Terms of Use](http://www.gap.com/Asset_Archive/GPWeb/content/0008/000/Dynamic/US/en_US/gapsplash.html).

back to top

### What if I use different devices to visit Gap Inc. websites or mobile applications?

In order to provide you with a more efficient and convenient shopping experience, you may be able to access various content or sign into your account from many different devices. If you use different devices (such as your home computer, laptop, mobile device and/or an intelligent personal assistant device) to access our sites or our mobile applications and/or place a transaction with or request services from one of our brands, we may be able to associate you with each of your devices. For example, our sites may allow you to access your favorite items or shopping cart via an email link that is unique to your account. By clicking on the link, you will be automatically signed into your account in order for you to continue your shopping experience where you left off. If you choose to click the email link on a new device, we will be able to associate your current device with your account information. 

Information we have collected from your different devices may be combined with other information you have provided us, including details about: information that is saved in your customer account; your transactional history with our brands; how you use our sites, apps and services; the products you view or services and features or in-store technologies in which you choose to interact. We may use such information to help provide more tailored experiences and consistent services and experiences across all of your devices as explained in this privacy notice. We also may use this information to prevent fraud, such as by identifying when your account is accessed from an unfamiliar device, or to provide customized offers or advertising based on your use of each device and your interactions with our brands, services and offerings Please refer to the “Cookies” section to learn how you can exercise choices regarding cookie-based tracking, or refer to the section “How is my information used for behavioral or targeted advertising and what choices do I have?” to learn more about your choices regarding online advertising. 

back to top

### Why did I receive a marketing email after I made a purchase in a Gap Inc. store?

To provide you with a more seamless customer experience, we keep records of all your Gap Inc. transactions, both online and in-store. For example, if you use a credit or debit card or give the sales associate your email address when you make a purchase in our store, we may associate that information with your online customer account. As described above, we may use information about your purchases to email you about other products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

back to top

### How do I access or change my information?

You can review and change certain personal information related to your use of our online sites (such as your name and contact information). To access your information at a Gap Inc. website, simply sign in to your account using your email address and password, and you will be able to edit your personal information in your account profile.

You can also ask us to update your personal information by contacting us as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below. Please note that any request to update your personal information may take up to 10 days for your email request and 6-8 weeks for your postal mail request.

back to top

### How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?

Gap Inc. and our brands, including Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory, Banana Republic Factory, and Athleta, want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers and sales events, from one or more of our brands, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below or you can click on the self-service unsubscribe links below.  
Athleta Unsubscribe

If contacting customer service, please be sure to include your full name and the email address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from the Gap Inc. brand. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Gap Inc.

If you change your mind, you can start receiving promotional communications from us again by logging into your online account and changing your preferences, by signing up when you visit our websites or our stores or when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, or by contacting customer service.

Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.

back to top

### How do I stop receiving Athleta catalogs?

If you no longer wish to receive Athleta catalogs or wish to alert us to duplicate mailings, please contact Athleta customer service as described in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below. Please provide your exact name, postal address, and email address so that your request can be effectively processed. It may take up to 90 days in order for your information to be completely removed from our list.

To learn more about your rights as a consumer and to receive less national advertising mail, please visit the Direct Marketing Association at [http://www.dmachoice.org/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

back to top

### What if I interact or make a purchase with Weddington Way? 

Weddington Way is a member of the Gap Inc. family of companies. When you visit Weddington Way’s website, interact with their services or make a purchase, your data is being collected and handled by Weddington Way under its privacy policy. Weddington Ways’s data collection and use practices may differ from Gap Inc.’s other brands. For example, Weddington Way, like other retailers, may share your personal information with other businesses and organizations (“Promotional Partners”) so that they can provide you with information about products and services that may interest you. 

For full details on how Weddington Way uses your data and for details on your choices, read [Weddington Way’s Privacy Policy](https://www.weddingtonway.com/privacy_policy). 

back to top

### How does Gap Inc. protect kids' privacy?

Gap Inc. is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our websites are general audience sites and are not targeted to or intended for use by children.

back to top

### How is my information used for behavioral or targeted advertising and what choices do I have?

We use our own cookies to help determine which of our ads are shown to you on other websites. To opt out of this targeted online advertising by Gap Inc. that utilizes our cookies, please click [here](http://dtmc.gap.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=3134&cname=The%20Gap&cmagic=35937e&clogo=3134.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). 

We also work with third-party companies that use their tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) on our websites in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your activity on our sites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications and use this information to determine which ads you see on third-party websites and applications. These technologies and the information collected about you may also be used to track your activity across multiple devices. For more information about this practice and to understand your options including how to opt out of receiving these tailored advertisements, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

Please note that even if you opt-out, these tracking technologies may still collect data and you will still see ads, but they will not be targeted based upon the information collected through these tracking technologies. 

back to top

### What if I apply for a Gap Inc. branded credit card on your site?

We may provide you with opportunities to apply for an offer of credit from a payment card issuer in our stores or online. To create a more convenient application process, we may provide information from your customer account to a payment card issuer in order to generate a pre-approved credit offer and/or prepopulate your online credit card application with information from your customer account. By submitting a credit card application either in store or online, you acknowledge and agree that Gap Inc. may provide your information to the payment card issuer in accordance with the terms and conditions of the application. For information about the privacy practices associated with your credit card application, please contact the payment card issuer. 

back to top

### What if I participate in local store programs?

We may provide special opportunities for customers in certain stores or locations to receive personalized shopping or other services, such as notification when your favorite products will be in your local store, product recommendations, unique offers for certain community members such as teachers or fitness instructors, and invitations to special local events. 

In order to provide these personalized services, a sales associate may ask for information about your interests, activities, shopping preferences and other people for whom you are shopping. We may also keep records of your sizing preferences, product wish lists, local store transaction history, and contact information. We may use your information to contact you by phone or text message, in accordance with this policy. In certain instances, you may also be able to authorize a sales associate to make purchases on your behalf using payment information you have previously provided during an online or in-store transaction. 

back to top

### How do I know my personal information is secure?

We do our best to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to help protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, or if you're not quite comfortable shopping online at any of our websites, please feel free to place your order with us by telephone at the number listed in the section entitled, "How do I contact you?", below.

back to top

### What is "phishing"?

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.

back to top

### I received a suspicious email from a Gap Inc. brand regarding an order I did not place. What should I do?

We are aware of phony emails sent out under our brand names. These emails did not originate from Gap Inc., and individuals who received fraudulent order status emails have not been charged. For your protection, do not click links or open any files attached to suspicious, unsolicited emails. If you believe your personal computer has been compromised as a result of the scam, please consult an IT professional. For more information, contact the FBI's Internet Crimes Complaint Center: [http://www.ic3.gov](http://www.ic3.gov/). We work with law enforcement on their investigations of these kinds of fraudulent emails.

back to top

### I responded to an online job posting for a Gap Inc. job that requires me to upload personal financial information. Is this part of your hiring process?

No. Gap Inc. does not ask prospective job applicants for information about their bank accounts, credit history or passwords to financial accounts. If you are asked for personal financial or security information in response to a job application, this is likely a fraudulent job listing hosted by spammers posing as Gap Inc. to mislead job applicants. You can validate all Gap Inc. job postings on <http://www.gapinc.com/careers>. Spammers also create phony aliases such as thegap-usa.com to mimic our company and/or brand names in an effort to commit identity theft or other forms of fraud. If you receive this type of suspicious email activity, please alert the FBI's Internet Crimes Complaint Center: [http://www.ic3.gov](http://www.ic3.gov/)

back to top

### What about links to other websites?

For your convenience and information, our websites may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our sites.

back to top

### How do I contact you?

For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, to update your personal information, or to place an order, you can contact any of our Gap Inc. brands by email, telephone, or postal mail:

_Gap Customer Services_  
100 Gap Online Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123  
1-800-GAPSTYLE (1-800-427-7895)  
1-888-906-1104 (TDD hearing impaired)  

_Banana Republic Customer Services_  
5900 North Meadows Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123-8476  
1-888-BR STYLE (1-888-277-8953)  
1-888-906-1345 (TDD hearing impaired)  

_Old Navy Customer Services_  
200 Old Navy Lane  
Grove City, OH 43123-8605  
1-800-653-6289  
1-800-449-4253 (TDD hearing impaired)  

_Athleta Customer Service_  
5900 North Meadows Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123  
1-877-3ATHLETA (1-877-328-4538)  
1-888-906-1345 (TDD hearing impaired)  

_Gap Factory Customer Services_  
100 Gap Online Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123  
1-844-GFS-ONLINE (1-844-437-6654)  
1-888-906-1104 (TDD hearing impaired)  

_Banana Republic Factory Customer Services_  
5900 North Meadows Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123-8476  
1-844-273-7746   
1-888-906-1345 (TDD hearing impaired)   

back to top

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Gap Inc. who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:

Gap Inc. - California Privacy Rights  
Legal Department  
2 Folsom Street  
San Francisco, CA 94105 

### California Do Not Track Disclosure

Do Not Track is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on the Do Not Track signal, the browser sends a message to websites requesting them not to track the user. At this time, we do not respond to Do Not Track browser settings or signals. For information about Do Not Track, please visit: [www.allaboutdnt.org](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/).

back to top

## Política de Privacidad

_Última Revisión: 12 de abril de 2017_

Esta política describe la información personal o datos personales que Gap Inc. y nuestras marcas, que incluyen sin limitación, Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory, Banana Republic Factory, y Athleta (de manera colectiva, "Gap Inc.") recaban acerca de usted, por qué los recabamos, cómo los utilizamos y cuándo los compartimos con terceros. Tome nota por favor que esta política no cubre la recopilación de datos y los usos de Weddington Way, como se describirá más abajo. Para mayores detalles sobre como Weddington Way puede recopilar, utilizar y compartir sus datos personales, véase la [Política de Privacidad de Weddington Way](https://www.weddingtonway.com/privacy_policy).

Esta política cubre nuestras tiendas en los Estados Unidos de América y experiencias en línea incluyendo nuestros sitios web y aplicaciones móviles y otras páginas web y servicios que operamos y en los cuales publicamos un enlace directo con esta política. Nuestra política también describe las opciones que tiene en relación a la forma en la que recabamos sus datos personales y cómo los utilizamos. Si cambian nuestras prácticas de protección de datos, publicaremos una política actualizada en nuestro sitio web. Podrá constatar que la política ha cambiado si verifica la fecha de revisión que aparece arriba. Si cambiamos la política de manera sustancial, le notificaremos apropiadamente. Podrá decidir sobre las opciones que tiene en relación a cómo recabamos y utilizamos sus datos personales de acuerdo con esta política en cualquier momento.

Si tiene dudas acerca de nuestra política de privacidad, por favor contáctenos como se describe en la sección titulada, ""¿Cómo puedo contactarlos?" ,incluida más adelante.

  * ¿Qué tipo de información recaba Gap Inc.?
  * ¿Cómo Gap Inc. utiliza mi información?
  * ¿Cómo Gap Inc. comparte mi información?
  * ¿Qué otra información recaba Gap Inc.?
  * ¿Qué pasa si me conecto a los servicios de Wi-Fi en las tiendas de Gap Inc.?
  * ¿Qué pasa si utilizo diferentes dispositivos para visitar sitios web de Gap Inc. o aplicaciones móviles?
  * ¿Por qué he recibido un correo electrónico de marketing después de hacer una compra en una tienda de Gap Inc.?
  * ¿Cómo accedo o cambio mis datos personales?
  * ¿Cómo puedo optar por no recibir comunicaciones promocionales?
  * ¿Cómo dejo de recibir los catálogos de Athleta?
  * ¿Qué sucede si interactúo o hago una compra con Weddington Way?
  * ¿Cómo protege Gap Inc. la privacidad de los niños?
  * ¿Cómo se utilizan mis datos personales para publicidad dirigida o basada en comportamiento y qué opciones tengo?
  * ¿Qué sucede si solicito una tarjeta de crédito de la marca Gap Inc. en su sitio?
  * ¿Qué sucede si participo en programas de tiendas locales?
  * ¿Cómo sé que mis datos personales están seguros?
  * ¿Qué es "phishing"?
  * Recibí un correo electrónico sospechoso de alguna marca de Gap Inc. con relación a una compra que no realicé. ¿Qué debo hacer?
  * Respondí a un aviso de empleo en línea para un trabajo en Gap Inc. que me solicita proporcionar datos personales financieros. ¿Es esto parte del proceso de contratación?
  * ¿Qué hay acerca de los enlaces a otros sitios web?
  * ¿Cómo puedo contactarlos?
  * Su Derecho a la Privacidad en California

### ¿Qué tipo de información recaba Gap Inc.?

Podemos recabar datos personales de Usted, tal como su nombre, dirección de correo electrónico, dirección postal, número de teléfono, número de tarjeta de crédito, sexo, cumpleaños, intereses personales, etc. cuando visita uno de nuestros sitios web o tiendas, instala o utiliza nuestras aplicaciones móviles, realiza un pedido en línea o por teléfono, hace una compra en nuestras tiendas, almacena su información en línea, se pone en contacto con nosotros para hacernos una pregunta o manifestar una preocupación, o participa en un concurso, promoción o encuesta. Mantenemos un registro de los productos que le interesan y las compras que realiza en línea, a través de una aplicación móvil, por teléfono o en nuestras tiendas.

Podemos combinar su información personal con información sobre sus transacciones y otras interacciones con nosotros llevadas a cabo en línea y en las tiendas, incluyendo sus compras. También podemos combinar su información personal con información que recibimos de otras fuentes, como de socios conjuntos de marketing, bases de datos públicas, páginas públicas en redes sociales y otros terceros. Además, si decide participar en intercambio social, como por ejemplo conectando su cuenta de redes sociales a su cuenta de cliente o ingresando a su cuenta de cliente a través de su cuenta de redes sociales, el sitio de la red social puede compartir información con nosotros acerca del uso de sus servicios, incluyendo información de perfil, información sobre sus contactos y el contenido que ha visto o que le ha gustado. Por favor, consulte las opciones de privacidad del sitio de la red social a fin de controlar cómo se comparte su información.

Si envía cualquier información personal relacionada a otras personas, a nosotros o a nuestros proveedores de servicios, declara que tiene la autorización para hacerlo, así como para permitirnos utilizar la información de acuerdo con esta Política de Privacidad.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo Gap Inc. utiliza mi información?

Podemos utilizar su información personal de las siguientes maneras:

  * Para procesar y cumplir con su pedido, incluyendo el envío de correos electrónicos para confirmar el estado del pedido y el envío
  * Para comunicarnos con usted y enviarle información por correo electrónico, correo postal, teléfono, mensaje de texto, u otros medios sobre nuestros productos, servicios, concursos y promociones, incluyendo comunicaciones de marketing que creemos pueden ser de su interés
  * Para hacer su experiencia de compra más fácil, más agradable y más eficiente
  * Para hacer frente a problemas con nuestros productos, marcas, servicios y tecnologías, y mejorarlos, así como desarrollar nuevos productos y servicios
  * Para permitirle el uso de nuestras tecnologías en las tiendas y en línea
  * Para proporcionar servicios consistentes y personalizados en todos los canales y todas nuestras marcas, incluyendo para personalizar nuestra publicidad, comunicaciones de marketing, su experiencia de compra y ofertas promocionales
  * Organizar eventos de la comunidad local, promociones y experiencias en las tiendas
  * Para facilitar el intercambio social
  * Para permitirle que solicite un crédito de un proveedor de tarjetas de crédito
  * Para permitirle que se inscriba y participe en un programa de lealtad o de relación con clientes
  * Para administrar y llevar a cabo nuestros concursos y otras promociones
  * Para conocer más acerca de sus preferencias de compra
  * Para prevenir, detectar, investigar y mitigar fraudes, violaciones de seguridad y actividades que están o pueden estar prohibidas o son ilegales
  * Para hacer cumplir nuestros [Términos y Condiciones](http://athleta.gap.com/customerService/info.do?cid=44990) y otras políticas
  * En la medida en que consideremos necesario o apropiado, para proteger los derechos, propiedad y seguridad de Gap Inc. y nuestros empleados, clientes y terceros
  * En la medida que consideremos que es necesario o apropiado bajo las leyes aplicables, para responder a las peticiones de autoridades gubernamentales y cumplir con procesos legales

Usted siempre tiene la opción de no recibir información de marketing o llamadas. Para saber como dejar de recibir información de marketing y llamadas, consulte la sección titulada, "¿Cómo puedo optar por no recibir comunicaciones promocionales?" ,incluida mas adelante.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo Gap Inc. comparte mi información?

Podemos compartir sus datos e información personal de las siguientes maneras:

  * **Marcas.** Cuando usted proporciona información personal a una de las marcas de Gap Inc. (Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory, Banana Republic Factory, Athleta o Intermix), podemos compartir esa información con las otras marcas de Gap Inc. 
  * **Correo directo.** Si usted compra productos de la marca Athleta a través de nuestro sitio web o mediante una orden de catálogo por teléfono o correo, podemos compartir su nombre, dirección postal y su historial de compra con organizaciones afines para finalidades de marketing por correo directo. No compartimos direcciones de correo electrónico para tales fines. Asimismo, no compartimos información personal sobre los clientes que únicamente navegan por nuestro sitio, envían comentarios por correo electrónico, solicitan un catálogo o alertas de correo o que solamente compran productos Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory, Banana Republic Factory o Intermix. Si usted prefiere que no compartamos su información con otras compañías, por favor háganoslo saber poniéndose en contacto con el departamento de servicio al cliente de Athleta como se describe en la sección titulada, "¿Cómo puedo contactarlos?"incluida más adelante.
  * **Por Usted.** Es posible que revele información personal cuando sube contenido a nuestros sitios web, a las tecnologías en las tiendas u otros foros públicos, tales como las páginas de nuestras marcas en redes sociales, blogs y comentarios de nuestros productos en línea. Cualquier información que usted divulgue a través de estos servicios se hará pública.
  * **Compartiendo socialmente.** Su información personal puede ser revelada en relación con su actividad de intercambio social, por ejemplo, si accede a su cuenta de cliente a través de su cuenta de redes sociales. Mediante la conexión de su cuenta de cliente y su cuenta en redes sociales nos autoriza a compartir información con su proveedor de redes sociales y entiende que el uso de la información que compartimos se regirá por la política de privacidad de la red social.
  * **Proveedores de servicio.** Podemos compartir su información con nuestros proveedores de servicios quienes manejan información de nuestros clientes y llevan a cabo servicios a nuestro nombre, tales como cumplimiento de las promociones, envío de comunicaciones, elaboración de encuestas, etc. Estos proveedores de servicios no están autorizados para llevar a cabo otro uso o divulgar su información. 
  * **Terceros.** Podemos compartir su información cuando hacemos equipo con otra compañía para ofrecer o proporcionar productos, servicios, concursos o promociones a nuestros clientes.
  * **Requerimientos legales.** Podemos compartir información sobre usted, si a nuestro juicio es necesario o apropiado, para cumplir con las leyes y reglamentos o en respuesta a un requerimiento, orden o solicitud gubernamental válidos, o para proteger las operaciones, privacidad, seguridad, propiedad o los derechos de Gap Inc. u otros.
  * **Programas Scrip o de lealtad.** Si decide participar en cualquier programa de lealtad, programa scrip de terceros o cualquier otro programa similar en el que una marca de Gap Inc. sea un proveedor participante, y autoriza a Gap Inc. o a nuestro procesador de tarjetas de crédito a proporcionar información sobre sus compras a la compañía que administra el programa, compartiremos dicha información con el administrador. Los programas Scrip le permiten darnos instrucciones para desviar un porcentaje de la cantidad que gasta en compras de Gap Inc. a las escuelas participantes y otras organizaciones no lucrativas. Los programas de lealtad le permiten acumular "puntos" en compras de productos de las marcas de Gap Inc., que pueden utilizarse para adquirir ciertas recompensas ofrecidas por los programas de lealtad en los que participe. La información que nos autoriza a revelar a los Programas Scrip o programas de lealtad de terceros puede incluir su número de tarjeta de crédito y la fecha y la cantidad de su compra, así como su nombre y otra información que nos ha solicitado compartir. Tenga en cuenta que una vez que compartimos su información, la compañía del programa Scrip o del programa de lealtad pueden utilizarla y compartirla de acuerdo con sus propias políticas de privacidad. Le pedimos revisar cuidadosamente dichas políticas puesto que no tenemos control sobre ellas.
  * **Transferencia del negocio.** En el improbable caso de una venta o fusión de Gap Inc. o cualquiera de nuestros negocios, la información personal de nuestros clientes y otra información que hemos recabado conforme a lo que se describe en esta política puede ser uno de los activos transferidos.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Qué otra información recaba Gap Inc.?

Podemos recabar información que no revela su identidad o que no se refiere directamente a una persona, tal como información del navegador y el dispositivo; información recabada a través de cookies, etiquetas de píxel y otras tecnologías, información demográfica y otra información que usted nos proporciona; así como información agregada.

Podemos utilizar y revelar dicha información para cualquier propósito legal. De ser necesario, trataremos dicha información como información personal de acuerdo con esta política. También trataremos dicha información como personal en la medida en que se combine con información personal. Por ejemplo, cuando utiliza nuestra tecnología, podremos mantener un registro de los productos que le interesan, las compras que hace y otros contenidos que genere (como los productos que agrega a su carrito de compras).

Podemos recabar información de diferentes formas, incluyendo a través de:

  * **Su navegador o dispositivo:** Cierta información es recabada por la mayoría de los navegadores o automáticamente a través de su dispositivo, tal como el Control de Acceso al Medio (MAC, por sus siglas en inglés), el tipo de ordenador (Windows o Macintosh), resolución de pantalla, el nombre del sistema operativo y versión, fabricante del dispositivo y modelo, idioma, tipo de navegador de Internet y versión, y la información de uso y datos de destino del navegador.
  * **Aplicaciones móviles:** Al descargar y utilizar una de nuestras aplicaciones móviles, podemos rastrear y recabar datos de uso, tales como la fecha y hora en la que la aplicación en el dispositivo accede a nuestros servidores y qué información y archivos se han accedido, visto y/o descargado a la aplicación, en función de su número de dispositivo u otro identificador.
  * **Cookies:** Las cookies son fragmentos de información almacenada directamente en el equipo que está utilizando. Nuestros sitios web, publicidad en línea, y correos electrónicos usan cookies, etiquetas de píxel y otras tecnologías para recabar automáticamente información acerca de sus interacciones, tales como el tipo de navegador, páginas visitadas, enlaces en los que hace clic, y otras acciones que realiza en relación con nuestros sitios web, anuncios en línea, y correo electrónico. Utilizamos esa información para varios propósitos, incluyendo, para facilitar la navegación, mostrar la información de manera más eficaz, personalizar su experiencia, entender cómo se utilizan nuestros sitios web, medir el éxito de nuestras campañas de marketing y por motivos de seguridad. Si su navegador está configurado para rechazar las cookies, no podrá acceder a su cuenta de cliente o realizar compras en nuestros sitios web. Para entender cómo utilizamos las cookies para publicidad, vea por favor la sección "¿Cómo se utilizan mis datos personales para publicidad dirigida o basada en comportamiento y qué opciones tengo?" ,incluida más adelante.

Si no desea que cierta información se recabe a través del uso de cookies, hay un procedimiento simple en la mayoría de los navegadores que le permite rechazar automáticamente las cookies o tiene la opción de rechazar o aceptar la transferencia al ordenador de una cookie (o cookies) en particular de un sitio específico. Si no acepta las cookies, puede experimentar algunos inconvenientes en el uso de nuestros sitios web. Por ejemplo, es posible que no pueda acceder a la información de su cuenta o realizar una compra en nuestros sitios web.

  * **El uso de etiquetas de píxel y otras tecnologías similares:** Podemos utilizar etiquetas de píxel para, entre otras cosas, dar seguimiento a las acciones de los usuarios de nuestros sitios web y los servicios (incluyendo los destinatarios de correo electrónico), medir el éxito de nuestras campañas de marketing y compilar estadísticas sobre el uso de nuestros sitios y servicios y el índice de respuesta.
  * **Analytics:** Utilizamos proveedores de servicios como Google y Adobe, quienes utilizan cookies y otras tecnologías similares para recabar y analizar información sobre el uso de nuestros sitios web, aplicaciones móviles y tecnologías en tiendas. Este servicio también puede recopilar información sobre el uso de otros sitios web, aplicaciones y recursos en línea. Puede conocer las prácticas de Google en <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>, y optar por no sujetarse a ellas utilizando el Add-on de Navegador de Rechazo de Google Analytics, disponible en <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. Puede conocer las prácticas de Adobe y optar por usar o no la tecnología de Adobe en <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html>.
  * **Adobe Flash:** Podemos utilizar la tecnología Adobe Flash, incluyendo Flash Local Shared Objects ("Flash LSOs"), y otras tecnologías similares para recabar y almacenar información sobre el uso de nuestros sitios web y aplicaciones móviles. Usted puede ajustar la configuración del reproductor de Flash para bloquear el almacenamiento Flash LSOs en su ordenador utilizando las herramientas contenidas en el [Panel de Ajustes de Almacenamiento de Sitios Web](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). También puede controlar los Flash LSOs yendo al [Panel de Configuración de Almacenamiento Global](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html) y siguiendo las instrucciones (que pueden incluir instrucciones que explican, por ejemplo, cómo eliminar Flash LSOs (referida como "información" en el sitio de Macromedia), cómo prevenir que se instalen Flash LSOs en su computadora sin que se le pregunte, y (para Flash Player 8 y posteriores) la forma de bloquear Flash LSOs que no son entregados por el operador de la página en la que se encuentra en ese momento). Tome en cuenta que el ajuste del reproductor Flash para limitar la aceptación de Flash LSOs puede interferir con el funcionamiento de algunas aplicaciones de Flash, incluyendo aquellas utilizadas en relación con nuestros sitios web y aplicaciones móviles.
  * **Dirección de IP:** Su dirección de Protocolo de Internet ("IP") es un número que asigna el proveedor de servicios de Internet automáticamente a la computadora que Usted está utilizando. Una dirección de IP puede ser identificada y registrada automáticamente en nuestros archivos de registro del servidor cada vez que accede a nuestros sitios web, junto con la hora de su visita y las páginas visitadas. Su dirección de IP también puede indicar su ubicación física aproximada. La recopilación de direcciones de IP es una práctica estándar y se lleva a cabo automáticamente por muchos sitios web, aplicaciones y otras tecnologías. Utilizamos las direcciones de IP para calcular el nivel de uso y diagnosticar problemas del servidor.
  * **Ubicación física:** Podemos recabar la ubicación física de su dispositivo, por ejemplo, a través del uso de satélites, señales de torres de telefonía celular o Wi-Fi. Podemos utilizar la ubicación física de su dispositivo para ofrecerle contenido y servicios personalizados basados en la localización del dispositivo. Usted puede permitir o negar tales usos, sin embargo, si decide no permitirlos o negarlos no podremos proporcionarle una experiencia de usuario personalizada.
  * **Tecnología dentro de las tiendas:** Podremos proporcionar tecnología en las tiendas para ayudar a personalizar y mejorar su experiencia de compra. Estas tecnologías requieren la recolección de cierta información de su dispositivo móvil, tal como la dirección MAC u otra información de identificación del dispositivo y pueden permitirle facilitar datos personales para aumentar el nivel de personalización, tal como sus intereses, preferencias de compra e información en relación con su talla. 
  * **Información agregada:** Podremos recabar y utilizar información agregada, que no lo identifica personalmente. Por ejemplo, podemos calcular el porcentaje de usuarios de nuestros sitios web que tienen un mismo código de área telefónica.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Qué pasa si me conecto a los servicios de Wi-Fi en las tiendas de Gap Inc.?

Si elige conectarse a nuestros servicios Wi-Fi dentro de las tiendas, Gap Inc. recibirá información sobre usted y su dispositivo, incluyendo la dirección MAC del dispositivo, la dirección de IP, el indicador de intensidad de señal (RSSI) y detalles técnicos del dispositivo, tales como su sistema operativo y el tipo de dispositivo (incluyendo marca y modelo) y las capacidades técnicas. Si usted ha dado un nombre a su dispositivo también podremos conocerlo. También recibiremos información sobre cómo utiliza nuestra red Wi-Fi mientras está conectado, incluyendo la ubicación de la tienda, las áreas de la tienda que visita, los nombres y/o direcciones de Internet de los sitios web que visita, las aplicaciones que utiliza, y el tiempo que interactúa con dichos sitios o aplicaciones. Recabaremos esta información cada vez que se conecte a nuestros servicios Wi-Fi y la misma podrá asociarse con otra información que hemos recopilado de usted y sobre usted.

Si su dispositivo móvil está configurado para buscar redes Wi-Fi disponibles, podremos recibir información acerca de su dispositivo incluso si elige no conectarse a nuestros servicios de Wi-Fi.

Para su conveniencia, podemos ofrecerle una opción para permanecer conectado a las redes de Wi-Fi de Gap Inc. Si elige esta opción, se conectará automáticamente a la red Wi-Fi de cualquier tienda de Gap Inc. que ofrezca servicios de Wi-Fi, y podremos recopilar la información descrita anteriormente, incluso si no utiliza el navegador de Internet o sus aplicaciones móviles durante el tiempo que esté en nuestra tienda. Usted puede optar por desconectarse de la red Wi-Fi de Gap Inc. en cualquier momento, a través de la configuración de Wi-Fi de su dispositivo. Sin embargo, tome en cuenta que desconectarse de la red Wi-Fi de una tienda únicamente lo desconectará de la red local durante su visita. Usted puede optar por salir de la función de conexión automática en cualquier momento visitando [http://www.smart-places.org](http://www.smart-places.org/).

Para más detalles sobre nuestras prácticas relacionadas con los servicios de Wi-Fi en nuestras tiendas, consulte nuestras [Condiciones de Uso de Wi-Fi](http://www.gap.com/Asset_Archive/GPWeb/content/0008/000/Dynamic/US/en_US/atsplash.html).

Volver al inicio

### ¿Qué pasa si utilizo diferentes dispositivos para visitar sitios web de Gap Inc. o aplicaciones móviles?

Con el fin de proporcionarle una experiencia de compra más eficiente y conveniente, Usted puede acceder a diversos contenidos o a su cuenta desde diferentes dispositivos. Si Usted utiliza diferentes dispositivos (tales como su ordenador personal, laptop, dispositivo móvil y/o asistente personal inteligente) para acceder a nuestros sitios o a nuestras aplicaciones móviles y/o hacer una transacción o solicitar servicios de una de nuestras marcas, podremos vincular con cada uno de sus dispositivos con su cuenta. Por ejemplo, nuestros sitios web pueden permitirle el acceso a sus artículos favoritos o carrito de compras a través de un enlace de correo electrónico que es único para su cuenta. Al hacer clic en el enlace, iniciará sesión automáticamente en su cuenta para continuar con su experiencia de compra donde la dejó. Si elige hacer clic en el enlace de correo electrónico de un nuevo dispositivo, podremos asociar dicho dispositivo con información de su cuenta. 

La información que hemos recabado de los diferentes dispositivos podrá ser combinada con otra información que nos ha proporcionado, incluyendo detalles sobre: información que guardó en su cuenta de cliente; su historial de transacciones con nuestras marcas; cómo utiliza nuestros sitios, aplicaciones y servicios; los productos que observa o los servicios y características o tecnología en nuestras tiendas con las cuales elige interactuar. Podemos utilizar dicha información para proporcionarle experiencias más personalizadas y servicios y experiencias consistentes a través de todos sus dispositivos, conforme a lo que se explica en la presente Política de Privacidad. Podemos también utilizar esta información para evitar fraude, por ejemplo, identificando cuando se accede a su cuenta desde un dispositivo no familiar o para proporcionar ofertas o anuncios personalizados con base en el uso de cada dispositivo y sus interacciones con nuestras marcas, servicios y ofertas. Refiarase a la sección "Cookies" para aprender cómo elegir el rastreo basado en cookies, o a la sección "¿Cómo se utilizan mis datos personales para publicidad dirigida o basada en comportamiento y qué opciones tengo?" para mayor información sobre sus opciones en materia de publicidad en línea. 

Volver al inicio

### ¿Por qué he recibido un correo electrónico de marketing después de hacer una compra en una tienda de Gap Inc.?

Para ofrecerle una mejor experiencia de compra, mantenemos un registro de todas sus transacciones con Gap Inc., ya sean en línea o en las tiendas. Por ejemplo, si utiliza una tarjeta de crédito o débito o si decide proporcionarle al vendedor que lo atendió su dirección de correo electrónico cuando hace una compra en nuestra tienda, podemos asociar esa información con su cuenta de cliente. Como se describió arriba, podremos utilizar la información acerca de sus compras para enviarle correos electrónicos sobre otros productos y servicios que consideramos pueden ser de su interés.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo accedo o cambio mis datos personales?

Usted puede revisar y actualizar algunos de sus datos personales relacionados con el uso de nuestros sitios web (tales como su nombre e información de contacto). Para acceder a su información en un sitio web de Gap Inc., regístrese simplemente en su cuenta utilizando su dirección de correo electrónico y contraseña, y podrá editar su información personal en su perfil de cuenta.

Puede también solicitar que nosotros actualicemos su información personal si nos contacta como se describe en la sección titulada "¿Cómo puedo contactarlos?"incluida mas adelante. Por favor tenga en cuenta que cualquier solicitud para actualizar sus datos personales puede tardar hasta 10 días, si es una solicitud por correo electrónico, y 6-8 semanas, si su solicitud es por correo postal.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo puedo decidir acerca de recibir comunicaciones promocionales?

Gap Inc. y nuestras marcas, incluyendo Gap, Banana Republic, Old Navy, Gap Factory, Banana Republic Factory, y Athleta. desean comunicarse con usted solamente si usted quiere saber de nosotros. Si prefiere no recibir información promocional o publicitaria, como información acerca de ofertas especiales y ventas de una o mas de nuestras marcas, puede hacérnoslo saber a través de nuestro servicio al cliente, tal y como se describe en la sección titulada "¿Cómo puedo contactarlos?" incluida más adelante o haciendo clic en los siguientes enlaces para anular su suscripción.  
Anular su suscripción a Athleta

Si contacta a servicio al cliente, por favor asegúrese de incluir su nombre completo y la dirección de correo electrónico que utilizó cuando se registró o hizo una compra con la marca de Gap Inc. Si nos solicita eliminar su nombre y dirección de nuestras listas promocionales, mantendremos su nombre en un archivo de "no contactar" para garantizar que podemos cumplir con su solicitud. El procesar su solicitud puede tardar hasta 10 días si se hizo por correo electrónico y 6-8 semanas si se hizo por correo postal; tiempo durante el cual podrá continuar recibiendo comunicaciones de Gap Inc. 

Si cambia de opinión, podrá empezar a recibir nuevamente nuestras comunicaciones promocionales ingresando a su cuenta en línea y cambiando sus preferencias, subscribiéndose cuando visite nuestro sitio web o tiendas o participando en un sorteo o concurso, o contactando a nuestro servicio al cliente.

Tome en cuenta que cuando hace una compra en línea con nosotros, confirmaremos el estatus de su pedido y envío por correo electrónico. Es posible que también lo contactemos por teléfono, correo electrónico o correo postal con preguntas o información sobre su pedido. 

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo dejo de recibir los catálogos de Athleta?

Si ya no desea recibir catálogos de Athleta o desea informarnos de correos duplicados, póngase en contacto con servicio al cliente de Athleta según lo descrito en la sección titulada, "¿Cómo puedo contactarlos?", incluida mas adelante. Indíquenos por favor su nombre, dirección postal y dirección de correo electrónico para que su petición pueda ser procesada de manera efectiva. Puede tardar 90 días para que su información esté totalmente borrada de nuestra lista.

Para mayores detalles sobre sus derechos como consumidor y para recibir menos correo publicitario nacional, visite la Direct Marketing Association en la dirección [http://www.dmachoice.org/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Volver al inicio

### ¿Qué sucede si interactúo o hago una compra con Weddington Way?

Weddington Way es un miembro de la familia de compañías de Gap Inc. Al visitar el sitio web de Weddington Way, interactuar con sus servicios o hacer una compra, sus datos son recopilados y manejados por Weddington Way bajo su política de privacidad. Las prácticas de recopilación y utilización de datos de Weddington Way pueden ser diferentes de las de otras marcas de Gap Inc. Por ejemplo, Weddington Way, como otros vendedores, puede compartir su información personal con otros negocios y organizaciones ("Socios Promocionales") para ofrecerle información sobre productos y servicios que pueden ser de interés para usted.

Para mayores detalles sobre cómo Weddington Way utiliza sus datos y para detalles sobre sus opciones, lea la [Política de Privacidad de Weddington Way.](https://www.weddingtonway.com/privacy_policy)

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo protege Gap Inc. la privacidad de los niños?

Gap Inc. está comprometido con la privacidad y seguridad de los niños cuando utilizan Internet. A sabiendas, nunca solicitaremos los datos personales una persona menor de 13 años de edad sin el consentimiento previo de sus padres. Nuestros sitios web son sitios para audiencia general y no están dirigidos ni destinados a ser utilizados por niños.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo se utilizan mis datos personales para publicidad dirigida o basada en comportamiento y qué opciones tengo?

Utilizamos cookies propias para ayudar a determinar cuáles de nuestros anuncios publicitarios le serán mostrados en otros sitios web. Para dejar de recibir publicidad dirigida en línea de Gap Inc., la cual utiliza nuestras cookies, por favor dé clic [aquí](http://dtmc.gap.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=3133&cname=Athleta&cmagic=7221e5&clogo=3133.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). 

Trabajamos también con otras empresas que usan sus propias tecnologías de seguimiento (incluyendo cookies y etiquetas de pixel) en nuestros sitios web con el fin de proporcionar anuncios publicitarios a la medida en nuestro nombre y en beneficio de otros anunciantes en Internet. Estas empresas podrán recabar información acerca de su actividad en nuestros sitios y su interacción con nuestra publicidad y demás comunicaciones, y utilizarán esta información para decidir qué anuncios publicitarios verá en sitios web y aplicaciones de terceros. Estas tecnologías y la información recopilada pueden también emplearse para rastrear su actividad entre varios dispositivos. Para mayor información acerca de esta práctica y para entender sus opciones incluyendo el optar por no recibir esta publicidad personalizada, por favor visite [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

Por favor tome en cuenta que aunque haya optado por no recibir publicidad personalizada, estas tecnologías podrán seguir recabando sus datos y seguirá viendo anuncios publicitarios, pero éstos no estarán dirigidos con base en la información que se recaba a través de estas tecnologías de seguimiento.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Qué sucede si solicito una tarjeta de crédito de la marca Gap Inc. en su sitio?

Es posible que le brindemos oportunidades para solicitar una oferta de crédito de un emisor de tarjetas de crédito en nuestras tiendas o en línea. Para crear un proceso de solicitud más conveniente, podemos proporcionar información de su cuenta de cliente a un emisor de tarjetas de crédito con el fin de que se genere una oferta de crédito pre-aprobado y/o pre-llenar su solicitud de tarjeta de crédito con información de su cuenta de cliente. Mediante la presentación de una solicitud de tarjeta de crédito, ya sea en la tienda o en línea, usted reconoce y acepta que Gap Inc. puede proporcionar su información al emisor de tarjetas de crédito de acuerdo con los términos y condiciones de la solicitud. Para obtener información sobre las prácticas de privacidad relacionadas con su solicitud de tarjeta de crédito, póngase en contacto con el emisor de la tarjeta de crédito.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Qué sucede si participo en programas de tiendas locales?

Podemos ofrecer oportunidades especiales para nuestros clientes en determinadas tiendas o localidades para recibir servicios personalizados de compras o de otros tipos, tales como notificaciones cuando sus productos favoritos estarán en la tienda, recomendaciones de productos, ofertas únicas para ciertos miembros de la comunidad, como maestros o instructores de acondicionamiento físico, e invitaciones a eventos especiales.

Con el fin de proporcionar estos servicios personalizados, un asociado de ventas puede solicitarle información acerca de sus intereses, actividades, preferencias de compra y las de otras personas para las que usted está haciendo compras. También podemos llevar un registro de sus preferencias de talla, lista de productos deseados, historial de transacciones en tienda e información de contacto. Podemos utilizar su información para contactarlo por teléfono o por mensaje de texto, de conformidad con esta política. En ciertas ocasiones, también puede autorizar a un asociado de ventas para realizar compras en su nombre utilizando la información de pago que haya proporcionado previamente durante una transacción en línea o en la tienda.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo sé que mis datos personales están seguros?

Hacemos nuestro mejor esfuerzo para brindarle una experiencia segura y conveniente. Contamos con medidas de seguridad física, electrónica, contractual y administrativa para proteger la seguridad y privacidad de sus datos personales.

Si por alguna razón no puede acceder al servidor seguro, o si no se siente muy cómodo al efectuar compras en línea en cualquiera de nuestros sitios web, no dude en hacer su pedido con nosotros vía teléfonica al número indicado en la sección titulada, "¿Cómo puedo contactarlos?" ,incluida más adelante.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Qué es "phishing"?

"Phishing" es un tipo de engaño diseñado para robar sus datos personales. Si recibe un correo electrónico que parezca que proviene de nosotros en el que le solicitemos datos personales, no lo responda. Nosotros nunca le solicitaremos su contraseña, nombre de usuario, información de tarjeta de crédito ni otros datos personales a través de correo electrónico.

Volver al inicio

### Recibí un correo electrónico sospechoso de alguna marca de Gap Inc. con relación a una compra que no realicé, ¿qué debo hacer?

Tenemos conocimiento de correos electrónicos falsos que se envían bajo los nombres de nuestras marcas. Estos correos electrónicos no tienen su origen en Gap Inc. y a los individuos que recibieron dichos correos fraudulentos con confirmación de estatus de pedido no se les aplicaron cargos. Para su protección, no dé clic en enlaces ni abra archivos adjuntos a correos electrónicos sospechosos o no solicitados. Si considera que su computadora personal ha sido afectada como resultado del engaño, por favor consulte a un profesional de TI. Para mayor información contacte al Centro de Quejas de Delitos por Internet (Internet Crimes Complaint Center) del FBI: [http://www.ic3.gov](http://www.ic3.gov/). Trabajamos con las autoridades en la investigación de este tipo de correos electrónicos fraudulentos.

Volver al inicio

### Respondí a un aviso de empleo en línea para un trabajo en Gap Inc. que me solicita proporcionar datos personales financieros. ¿Es esto parte del proceso de contratación?

No, Gap Inc. no les solicita a sus candidatos para empleo información acerca de sus cuentas bancarias, historial crediticio ni contraseñas de cuentas financieras. Si se le solicitan datos personales financieros o información de seguridad en respuesta a una solicitud de empleo, es muy probable que sea una oferta de empleo fraudulenta hecha por spammers haciéndose pasar por Gap Inc. para engañar a los solicitantes. Usted puede verificar todas las ofertas de trabajo de Gap Inc. en: <http://www.gapinc.com/careers>. Los spammers también crean alias falsos tales como thegap-usa.com para imitar a nuestra empresa y/o los nombres de nuestras marcas en un esfuerzo por cometer robo de identidad u alguna otra forma de fraude. Si usted recibe este tipo de correo electrónico sospechoso, por favor dé aviso al Centro de Quejas de Delitos por Internet (Internet Crimes Complaint Center) del FBI: [http://www.ic3.gov](http://www.ic3.gov/)

Volver al inicio

### ¿Qué hay acerca de los enlaces a otros sitios web?

Para su conveniencia e información, nuestros sitios web podrán contener enlaces a otros sitios, los cuales podrán tener sus propias políticas de privacidad que difieran de las nuestras. No somos responsables del contenido o prácticas de ningún sitio al que lleven los enlaces. Le recomendamos que revise las políticas de privacidad de cada sitio que visite a través de los enlaces de nuestros sitios.

Volver al inicio

### ¿Cómo puedo contactarlos?

Para preguntas acerca de nuestra política de privacidad, o para tomar decisiones acerca de la recepción de comunicaciones promocionales, para actualizar su información personal, o para hacer un pedido, usted puede contactar a cualquiera de nuestras marcas Gap Inc. por correo electrónico, teléfono o correo postal:

_Servicio al Cliente de Gap_  
100 Gap Online Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123  
1-800-GAPSTYLE (1-800-427-7895)  
1-888-906-1104 (TDD para personas con discapacidad auditiva)  

_Servicio al Cliente de Banana Republic_  
5900 North Meadows Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123-8476  
1-888-BR STYLE (1-888-277-8953)  
1-888-906-1345 (TDD para personas con discapacidad auditiva)  

_Servicio al Cliente de Old Navy_  
200 Old Navy Lane  
Grove City, OH 43123-8605  
1-800-653-6289  
1-800-449-4253 (TDD para personas con discapacidad auditiva)  

_Servicio al Cliente de Athleta_  
5900 North Meadows Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123  
1-877-3ATHLETA (1-877-328-4538)  
1-888-906-1345 (TDD para personas con discapacidad auditiva)  

_Servicio al Cliente de Gap Factory_  
100 Gap Online Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123  
1-844-GFS-ONLINE (1-844-437-6654)  
1-888-906-1104 (TDD para personas con discapacidad auditiva)  

_Servicio al Cliente de Banana Republic Factory_  
5900 North Meadows Drive  
Grove City, OH 43123-8476  
1-844-273-7746   
1-888-906-1345 (TDD para personas con discapacidad auditiva)  

Volver al inicio

### Su Derecho a la Privacidad en California

La Sección 1798.83 del Código Civil de California permite a los clientes de Gap Inc., con residencia en California, solicitar cierta información sobre la divulgación de datos personales a terceros para propósitos de marketing directo. Para hacer dicha solicitud, escríbanos a la siguiente dirección:

Gap Inc. - California Privacy Rights  
Legal Department  
2 Folsom Street  
San Francisco, CA 94105 

### Petición de no Rastrear. California

Do Not Track (No Rastrear) es una preferencia de privacidad que los usuarios pueden colocar en sus navegadores web. Cuando un usuario enciende la señal Do Not Track (No Rastrear), el navegador envía un mensaje a sitios web solicitando que no rastren al usuario. En este momento, no respondemos a los ajustes o señales de navegador Do Not Track (No Rastrear). Para información sobre Do Not Track (No Rastrear), visite: [www.allaboutdnt.org](http://www.allaboutdnt.org/).

Volver al inicio

back to top
